hi owner Roger
well
this is my last video you know
come to this tomorrow
is that day in retribution the team
richard
my revenge against human
against I love you last eight years of
my life
ever since I keep you reading have been
forced to endure
existence loans rejection
and unfulfilled desires because grooms
have never been attracted to me
girls gave their affection
sec two other men
but never to me and 22 years old
still virgin never even kissed a girl
have been to college
two and a half years more than that
actually
and I'm still virgin
has been very torturous
college is the time everyone experiences
since things such as sexting
time pleasure in those years I veterans
it's not fair
you girls have never been attracted to
me
I don't know why you girls are attracted
to me
I will punish you all for it it's an
injustice
a crime because I don't know what you
don't see me
the perfect guy you throw yourself
know these obnoxious man in Sydney
the supreme gentleman punish
I'll love you for with
the retribution I'm going to enter
the hard earnings UCSB
slaughter every singles
Boyle stop line like I see inside
their all those girls that desire so
much
they would have all rejected me in
down hmmm inferior man if I ever made a
sexual advance towards them
well they throw themselves at
these noxious group
take great pleasure slaughtering
view
you will finally see that I am true
the superior one the true alpha male
after I've nightly every single girl
in this take to the streets a violinist
slaney missing persons
popular kids live such lives
hedonistic pleasure well I've had rock
this for all these years
people look down upon me every time I
try to go out and join them
you know treat me like a mouse now
I will be a God compared to you while
the animals
you are an slider
again you
exacting retribution
all those who deserve you do deserve it
just for the crime
living a better life than me the popular
kids
never accepted me your
pay for
girls whatever one to love you
to be left by you want a girlfriend
want sex love
affection adoration you think a minority
that's a crime can never be forgiven
I can't have you guns
I will destroy you you tonight me
happy life intern
will deny all human life only fair
I hate
I love you humanity
casting wretched to train species
if I had it in my power I would stop at
nothing
to reduce every single one of you
to mountains and skulls rivers applied
rightfully so
deserve to pee nightly
Elgin T
you never showed me any mercy
so I'll show you mine
force me to suffer all my life now
make you suffer waited a long time for
this
gave you
exactly when you desire
you are you girls you
rejected me down upon me treated me like
scam
well you gave yourself and no human n
for living a better life than me he
sexually active men
hate you I hate own I can't wait to give
you exactly what you deserve
IDR Niamh Lynch
you